Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Clippings and Photocopies
  - Lotringer - "Gaston Ferdiéne", undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Lotringer "Autonomia" essay - published in Documents, mid-1980s (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - "A Conversation with Sylvere Lotringer" - photocopy of Conference 6:1, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Lotringer interview - Artscibe, undated (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Lotringer interview in Columbia magazine Conference, 1995-1996 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Lotringer published works copies, undated (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Articles by Lotringer / about Semiotext(e), undated (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Lotringer - "Sylvere Texts", undated (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Lotringer - various texts, undated (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Lyotard photocopy of "La critique, les minorities", undated (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Lyotard - photocopy of "Energumen Capitalism", Undated (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Lyotard photo clipped from paper, Undated (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Matthews, Harry - photocopy of "Lewis and Morris", Undated (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Mayer's Restorative Art, Undated (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Moles "Cybernetique et Oeuvre d'Art", Undated (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Montreal Mirror - copy, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Mueller, Cookie - "I hear America Sinking", Undated (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Muller - photocopies, Undated (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Myles, Eileen - "Bath, Maine", Undated (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Negri, Toni - "Contre le terrorisme d'Etat", November 1985 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - The New Yorker section, Undated (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - "No! Art" photocopies, Undated (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Le Nouvel Observateur - clippings, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Le Nouvel Observateur - clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Le Nouvel Observateur - clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 62, Folder 43)
  - O'Hara, Frank - poems, Undated (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Olson, Charles - "Projective Voice", Undated (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - "Paedagogia Historica", #33, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Proust - "Du cote du chez Swann", Undated (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Rattray, David - "In Nomine", Undated (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Ridon - "Romance Quarterly" - Andre Breton, Undated (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Robin Riddles - "Beyond the Real the Imaginary: Chris Kraus' 'How to shoot a crime' and other films", 1988 (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Roth, M. - Knowing and History - duplicates for indexing, Undated (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Roth, M. - Copies of essays of "Foucault, Friend", Undated (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Said - "Response" Liacritics, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - Saussure - copy of "calligrammes", Undated (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - "Saussure in French - Struct./Post. - Spring '05", Undated (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Schatzman - selections from "Soul Murder", Undated (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Sellers, Terrence - "Taking Flight", Undated (Box 62, Folder 57)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopy of "Le deux Saussure" vol. 2, no.1, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 58)
  - Semiotext(e) - "Ego Traps" vol. 1, no. 3, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 59)
  - Semiotext(e) - copy of "Ego Traps" - vol. 1, no. 3, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 60)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopy of "Forget Foucault" (Baudrillard), 1988 (Box 62, Folder 61)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopies of "Foucault Live", Undated (Box 62, Folder 62)
  - Semiotext(e) - copies from "Foucault Live", Undated (Box 62, Folder 63)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopies of original German issue, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 64)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopies of "Polysexuality", 1981 (Box 62, Folder 65)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopies of "Polysexuality", 1981 (Box 62, Folder 66)
  - Smith - from "Lectures on the Religion of the Semites", Undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Sophocles - "Oedipus the King", Undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Squires - "Is Richard Prince a Feminist?", Undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Strauss - "On Crack Wars" (Ronnell), Undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Tajima, Mike - printout of interview, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Tiefenbrun, Susan - copy of "La Belle Vieille de Francois Maynard", Undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Tillman, Lynne - copy of "Weird Fucks", Undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Tobin - photocopy of "New York's Jews and the Catskill Mountains", Undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Todorov - "How to Read", Undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Ullman, Stephen - "Phonologie et Point de vue Structural en Linguistique", Undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Urbain - "Le Toutourisme", Undated (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Village Voice Listings, July 20, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Voice Literary Supplement - Baudrillard and Deleuze clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Virilio - photocopy of "The Last Vehicle", Undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Virilio, Paul - "Futurisme et Facsisme", Undated (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Virilio, Paul - "Esthetique Disparition", Undated (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Welchman Artforum article "Face(t)s", 1988 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Unknown author - copy of "Commen se faire un Corps sans Organes?", undated (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Unknown author - photocopies of "Architecture of Death", 1982 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Unknown editor - "Discussion of the Work", undated (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Unknown author - copies from Futurist Theory and Invention, undated (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Unknown author - "Hildegarde, Solitaire de l'Apocalypse", undated (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Unknown author - page from "Hindrance of theory in critical work", undated (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Unknown author - "Histoire de la gousse et des lunettes" and other copies with underlining, undated (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Unknown author - "Operation Desert Storm", undated (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Unknown author - "La Poverta' in Ticino" [title page], Undated (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Unknown author - "The Question of Chinese Allegory", Undated (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Unknown author - "Le Roman Americain", Undated (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Unknown author - "Situationism", Undated (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Unknown author - "Surrealism" article, Undated (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Unknown author - "Two aspects of language and two types of aphasic disturbances", Undated (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Unknown author - selections from "Towards a New Vocabulary", Undated (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Unknown author - "Why Theory", Undated (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous poems, Undated (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous women writer's pieces, Undated (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous zine copies, Undated (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 53)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 55)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 56)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 59)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 61)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 64)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 66)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 67)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 68)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 69)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 70)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 63, Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Clippings from French newspapers, Undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, Undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Series IX: Editions of Publications
  Contains copies of Semiotext(e) Issues (Subseries A), Foreign and Native Agents series books (Subseries B), Sylvère Lotringer's publications (Subseries C), and foreign translations of Semiotext(e) and Lotringer's books (Subseries D). The books are arranged chronologically. In the case of the Semiotext(e) books in the first two subseries, preference has been given to including those books in the Downtown Collection if Fales did not already have a copy on the shelf. For issues of Semiotext(e) not found in this series, please check Bobcat: P99.S38. Books from the Foreign and Native Agents series' can be found by searching by author or title in Bobcat.
  - Subseries A: Semiotext(e) Issues
    - Semiotexte - "George Bataille" vol. II, no. 2, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Semiotexte - "George Bataille" vol. II, no. 2 (2), 1976 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Semiotexte - "Anti-Oedipus" vol. II, no. 3, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Semiotexte - "Anti-Oedipus" vol. II, no. 3, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Semiotexte - "Anti-Oedipus" vol. II, no. 3, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Semiotexte - "Nietzsche's Return" vol. III, no. 1, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Semiotexte - "Italy: Autonomia" vol. III, no. 3, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Semiotexte - "Polysexuality" vol. IV, no. 1, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Semiotexte - "Polysexuality" vol. IV, no. 1, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Semiotexte - "Polysexuality" vol. IV, no. 1, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Semiotexte - "Oasis" vol. IV, no. 3, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Semiotexte - "Oasis" vol. IV, no. 3, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Semiotexte USA, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Semiotexte USA, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Semiotexte 14 - SF, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Semiotexte 14 - SF, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Semiotexte 14 - SF, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Subseries B: Foreign and Native Agents Books
    - Baudrillard - "In the Shadow of the Silent Majorities and Other Essays" - book parts, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Baudrillard - "In the Shadow of the Silent Majorities", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Baudrillard - "In the Shadow of the Silent Majorities", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Baudrillard - "Simulations" - unbound, uncut pages, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Baudrillard - "Simulations", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Virilio, Paul and Lotringer, Sylvere - "Pure War", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Virilio, Paul and Lotringer, Sylvere - "Pure War", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Virilio, Paul and Lotringer, Sylvere - "Pure War", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Deleuze and Guattari - "On the Line", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - P.M. - "Bolo'bolo", 1985 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - P.M. - "Bolo'bolo", 1985 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Yurick, Sol - "Metatron"`, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Yurick, Sol - "Metatron", 1985 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Deleuze and Guattari - "Nomadology", 1986 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Virilio, Paul - "Speed and Politics", 1986 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Virilio, Paul - "Speed and Politics", 1986 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Baudrillard - "Forget Foucault", 1987 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Baudrillard - "The Ecstasy of Communications", 1988 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Ayden, Erje - "Sadness at Leaving", 1989 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Ayden, Erje - "Sadness at Leaving", 1989 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Foucault, Michele - "Foucault Live", 1989 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Pell, Derek - "Assassination Rhapsody", 1989 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Pell, Derek - "Assassination Rhapsody", 1989 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Guattari and Negri - "Communists Like Us", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Guattari and Negri - "Communists Like Us", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Guattari and Negri - "Communists Like Us", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Laederach, Jurg - "69 Ways to Play the Blues", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Laederach, Jurg - "69 Ways to Play the Blues", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Virilio, Paul - "Popular Defense and Ecological Struggles", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Baudrillard - "Fatal Strategies", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Foucault, Michel - "Remarks on Marx", 1991 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Foucault, Michel - "Remarks on Marx", 1991 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Virilio, Paul - "Politics of the Very Worst", 1999 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Mueller, Cookie - Walking Through Clear Water in a Pool Painted Blue", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Mueller, Cookie - "Walking Through Clear Water in a Pool Painted Blue", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Rower, Ann - "If You're a Girl", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Rower, Ann - "If You're a Girl", 1990 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Acker, Kathy - "Hannibal Lecter, My Father", 1991 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Acker, Kathy - "Hannibal Lecter, My Father", 1991 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Ludd, Deran - "Sick Burn Cut", 1992 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Myles, Eileen and Kotz, Liz (ed) - "The New Fuck You", 1995 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Myles, Eileen and Kotz, Liz (ed) - "The New Fuck You", 1995 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Myles, Eileen and Kotz, Liz (ed) - "The New Fuck You", 1995 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Kraus, Chris - "I Love Dick", 1997 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Kraus, Chris - "I Love Dick", 1997 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Kraus, Chris - "I Love Dick", 1997 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Tea, Michelle - "The Passionate Mistakes and Intricate Corruption of One Girl in America", 1998 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Subseries C: Sylvere Lotringer's Publications
    - Poetique 3: "Le Roman Impossible", 1970 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Critique 286: "Vice de Forme", 1971 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Poetique 12: "Mesure de la Demesure", 1972 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Literature no. 30: "Sade Incesticide", 1978 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Poetique 42: "Proust Polymorphe", 1980 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Semiotica: "Semiotics and Society", 1981 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Polysexuality (reprint of article): "Defunkt Sex", c. 1981 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Sacher-Masoch, Leopold Von - "Venus in Furs" (forward by Sylvere Lotringer), 1989 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Sacher-Masoch, Leopold Von - "Venus in Furs" (forward by Sylvere Lotringer), 1989 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Pataphysics - including Sylvere Lotringer and Chris Kraus interview, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere and Falkner, Gerhard (eds.) - "Am Lit", 1992 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Garnett, Eldon - "The Narrative Body" including "Ball of Fat" by Sylvere Lotringer, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Pataphysics K: "Never any Ever After", 1993 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Pataphysics no. 2: "Never Any Ever After", 1994 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Pataphysics no. 3: "A Visit with the Artists" - interview with Sylvere Lotringer, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere and Kraus, Chris (eds.) - "Hatred of Capitalism", 2001 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere - "Boules de Suif, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere - "The Game of the Name", Undated (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Subseries D: Foreign-Language Translations
    - Klappentexte 2/3 - German translation of Man/Boy love issue, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Alternative 145'46 - includes translation of Lotringer / Guattari interview, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Decode vol. 1 - Includes Lotringer interview (pg 56) with Jack Smith - Japanese translation, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Muller, Heiner - "Rotwelsch" - a dialogue with Sylvere Lotringer, first German version of [Marer], 1982 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere - "New Yorker Gesprache", 1983 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere - "New Yorker Gesprache", 1983 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere - "New Yorker Gesprache", 1983 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere and Virilio, Paul - "Der reine Krieg" (German version of "Pure War"), 1984 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Bohringer, Hannes; et al - "Philosophen-Kunstler" including Lotringer's "Und Seine Doubles", 1986 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Bakena nr. 9/10 - includes Lotringer's "Hyperrebelle", 1991 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Lotringer, Sylvere - "Foreign Agent" (translation of interviews), 1991 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - "Platz Machen" including Lotringer's "Nomadische Notizen", 1991 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Japanese book including Lotringer interview with Asada and a letter from the publisher, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Foucault, Michel - "Fearless Speech" (Japanese translation), 2002 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Series X: Video
  Arrangement
  Series X: Video is arranged chronologically. Undated materials are arranged alphabetically.
  Series X: Video contains video materials related to the films that Lotringer directed -- The Golden Bowl, or, Repression (1984-1989) and How to Shoot a Crime, which were co-directed with Chris Kraus; Too Sensitive to Touch (1981), co-directed with Michael Oblowitz; and solo works Second Hand Hitler (unfinished, circa 1985), Violent Femmes (1998), and The Man Who Disappeared (2015). Videos in this series include various edits of films, source materials, press appearances by Lotringer, footage from Lotringer's film studies, and films by his contemporaries. User discretion is advised for materials related to How to Shoot a Crime, which includes footage of real events.
  - Le Chagrin et la Pitie, circa 1969
    - Tape 1, ID 221.0136 (Box 79, Vhs ID 221.0136)
    - Tape 2, ID 221.0137 (Box 79, Vhs ID 221.0137)
  - Nova Convention materials, circa 1978
    - Tape 1 -- Interview with W.S. Burroughs, ID 221.0056 (Box 74, Vhs ID 221.0056)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Regional encoding: PAL
    - Tape 2 -- Interview with W.S. Burroughs, ID 221.0057 (Box 74, Vhs ID 221.0057)
    - Tape 3 -- HBO doc, 2000
      An off-air recording of the feature-length documentary "Into the Arms of Strangers: Stories of the Kindertransport" (2000).
      - Original video recording, ID 221.0058 (Box 74, Vhs ID 221.0058)
        Duration: 118 minutes
      - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 142, Dvd 221.0557)
    - Tape 4 -- Interview with W.S. Burroughs
      - Original video recording, ID 221.0059 (Box 74, Vhs ID 221.0059)
        Duration: 51 minutes
      - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 142, Dvd 221.0559)
    - Tape 5 -- Interview with W.S. Burroughs
      - Original video recording, ID 221.0060 (Box 74, Vhs ID 221.0060)
      - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 142, Dvd 221.0561)
  - The Set-Up, by Kathryn Bigelow, 1978
    - Original video recording, ID 221.0093 (Box 76, Vhs ID 221.0093)
      Duration: 16 minutes
    - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 144, Dvd 221.0385)
  - Lightning Over Water, circa 1980
    - First Version
      - Original video recording, ID 221.0081 (Box 75, Vhs ID 221.0081)
        Duration: 122 minutes; Standard: PAL
      - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 142, Dvd 221.0551)
    - Second Version
      - Original video recording, ID 221.0082 (Box 75, Vhs ID 221.0082)
        Duration: 90 minutes
      - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 142, Dvd 221.0552)
  - Tutuguri, by Raymonde Carasco, circa 1980
    One of four Raymonde Carasco tapes shown at the Antonin Artaud conference.
    - Original video recording, ID 221.0156 (Box 80, Vhs ID 221.0156)
      Duration: 23 minutes
    - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 142, Dvd 221.0565)
  - Too Sensitive to Touch, circa 1981
    - Original video recording, ID 221.0065 (Box 74, U-matic ID 221.0065)
    - Access DVD, ID 221.0065 (Box Shared Fales 144, Dvd 221.0375)
  - Too Sensitive to Touch -- Lotringer / Oblowicz, circa 1981; ID 221.0055 (Box 73, Vhs ID 221.0055)
  - Los Pintos, by Raymonde Carasco, circa 1982
    - Original video recording, ID 221.0153 (Box 80, Vhs ID 221.0153)
      Duration: 59 minutes
    - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 142, Dvd 221.0562)
  - Master of a Marion Scemama film made in Pier 72, circa 1982; ID 221.0064 (Box 74, U-matic ID 221.0064)
  - Interview footage for How to Shoot a Crime and Violent Femmes, 1982-1983, undated
    - Victoire Death, December 20, 1982
      - Original video recording, ID 221.0042 (Box 73, Vhs 221.0042)
        Duration: 123 minutes.
      - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 144, Dvd 221.0042)
    - Terry (Dub), February 10, 1983
      - Original video recording, ID 221.0045 (Box 73, Vhs 221.0045)
        Duration: 103 minutes
      - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 144, Dvd 221.0045)
    - Terry / Victoire, undated
      - Original video recording, ID 221.0046 (Box 73, Vhs 221.0046)
        Duration: 68 minutes
      - Access DVD (Box Shared Fales 144, Dvd 221.0046)
    - Tape 7, ID 221.0112 (Box 77, Vhs ID 221.0112)
    - Tape 8, ID 221.0113 (Box 77, Vhs ID 221.0113)
    - Tape 9, ID 221.0114 (Box 77, Vhs ID 221.0114)
    - Tape 10, ID 221.0115 (Box 77, Vhs ID 221.0115)
    - Tape 11, ID 221.0116 (Box 77, Vhs ID 221.0116)
  - Lotringer video on writer Pierre Guyotat, October 18, 1984
    - Tape 1, ID 221.0079 (Box 75, U-matic ID 221.0079)
    - Tape 2, ID 221.0080 (Box 75, Vhs ID 221.0080)
  - Second Hand Hitler -- First Version, August, 1985
    - Tape 1, ID 221.0075 (Box 75, U-matic ID 221.0075)
    - Tape 2, ID 221.0076 (Box 75, U-matic ID 221.0076)
    - Tape 3, ID 221.0077 (Box 75, Vhs ID 221.0077)
  - Chris Kraus short films -- Foolproof Illusion, Voyage of Rodez, Terrorist in Love, How to Shoot a Crime, circa 1985-1986; ID 221.0125 (Box 78, Vhs ID 221.0125)
    Duration: 53 minutes
  - Footage for Second Hand Hitler, circa 1985-1986
    - Tape 1 -- PAL, ID 221.0034 (Box 72, Vhs ID 221.0034)
    - Tape 2 -- PAL, ID 221.0035 (Box 72, Vhs ID 221.0035)
    - Tape 3 -- PAL, ID 221.0036 (Box 72, Vhs ID 221.0036)
    - Tape 4 -- PAL, ID 221.0037 (Box 72, Vhs ID 221.0037)